Hello everyone.
This is Kanramu.
Today's project is the first Oya King.
Puff puff puff.
This project is to see who knows the most about Otani Emery,
Last time we did King Noguchi,
Hana-chan won with 3.7 points.
3.7 points.
How confident are you today?
I would like to show them that I can take away Ohtani again this time.
Even if I take away Ohtani.
This is the first time I'm on this side of this project,
I can't lose, so I'm going to do my best here.
I'll be counting on you.
Let's get on with it.
First question.
What is the best thing you bought recently?
Eh?
Sounds like a wide range.
It's hard to choose a genre.
What do you call it, something that improves your life?
Oh, I don't know.
There's the A word, right?
Three letter A word.
CPQ.
QO.
QOL.
QOL up.
But I don't know. It's more like I'm excited about my life.
Today.
Wear it.
What's with that nice face?
You look a little nervous.
What? You're wearing it right now?
Oh, my God, that's a good look.
That's the look that all of mankind is going to say.
Yeah, it's true.
It's like I've been making this face for a long time because I don't have any Pensley's.
But I don't know... maybe it's not like I notice it or something.
Eeeee...
From a while ago.
Since a while ago.
What should I do?
I'm begging you.
Okay.
You said you didn't notice.
That may be true.
Because right now...
He was looking at our faces
"Flo" in our faces.
There you go.
I'll go with that.
Here's your answer.
This lip.
Ehhhh...
But it's 0.5.
Why?
Did you hear that last part?
What is it?
This lipstick.
L'illimieux Pink Fondue.
L'il Mu Pink Fondue.
That's the important part.
That was the end of the answer!
0.5
I got 4 points.
That's great.
You noticed the appeal.
I didn't do it.
I was doing it.
Shall we move on to the next question?
Here you go.
I don't like this Milinya.
What kind of Milinya?
That's what Milinya said, isn't it?
Well...
You'll be Mirinya.
Yes, yes, yes.
You know what I mean.
Cute?
No, it's not.
I don't want to see Milinya like this.
Well, if you write about the Milinya you don't want to see...
You know, if you write down the Milinya you don't want them to see, you'll win, right?
You'd win, wouldn't you?
Okay, okay.
Oh, that's good.
Oh, okay.
I like this Milinha.
I love it.
You love it.
She loves you.
Yes, I do.
Oh, good, you're early.
Game.
The game.
Oh, maybe I'll play too.
I'm in.Here we go.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
It's so lame, Mirinya.
Oh, it's so easy to understand.
I don't like it.
It's so lame. - It's so lame.
I'm a fashionista.
I don't want to see something so tacky.
Shaved head.
It looks good on you, doesn't it?
I think it looks good on you.
I think it'll look good on you.
It looks good on you.
It looks good.
But Miri's hair...
It's really unfair.
I don't have it.
You're right. She's a girl now.
Game on.
What's the answer?
I don't know.
Maybe not.
You've been blustering all day, Miryan.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, I see...
Ah...
It's her personality, not her looks.
I see.
Mirinya's always snarling at me.
I don't like it...
Can I ask you to wait?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hey, guess what?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Let me guess.
Excuse me.
I'll do my best.
Guess.
Let's move on to the next question.
If you were to be reincarnated as a member for a day, who would you be and what would you do?
Not similar.
No, we don't.
But maybe we all want to be.
But I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, my God.
Is it okay?
Yes!
Oh, I wrote it.
That's good.
OK!
Let's go.
Ready!
Ta-da!
I see.
I've always had the image of Miglia saying she admires you at first sight.
She does.
I think Chiara's fore-footedness and her loose, tension-free attitude are cute,
I have the image of Miria being surprisingly tension-free,
I thought it's like she wants to do something like this.
I'm lost.
I want to be like that.
Let's look at the convention.
Become Kiara and change into a free spirit.
Is that right?
It's the right answer.
Wow.
You guessed it. You're good.
I think everyone is a little bit good.
It's Chiara, too.
That's right.
She's a very attractive girl, isn't she?
I can understand the eyes.
I don't really want to scream out loud.
Shall we move on to the next question?
Yes, I do.
What are you secretly into now?
I haven't really told you.
I wonder.
But I think it's very easy to imagine.
Food?
Yes, yes, yes.
That kind.
Sweet, salty, spicy, bitter.
All of them.
All of them?
Are you into it?
Does he seem to be into it?
Hana doesn't seem to be into it. I don't think I'm into flowers.
I think I'm into it more than I'm not.
OK, maybe this is it. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Let's go!
Oh, what's that?
I ordered a lot of food from Uber Eats.
Wow! A hit gourmet food.Wow! A gourmet hit.
Wow, I see.
Both are good.
Coolness and...
Will I really win?
Hmmm... Oh, watching YouTubers who eat a lot of food.
Hey.
Hey!
No, you don't mean hey! You're not eating!
I didn't say anything about eating.
Wow!
That was totally different from when he rolled my palm.
I'm learning a lot. Thank you very much.
I will do the same when I do Uber.
I will.
Next question. Go ahead.
What was your best coming-of-age episode at Equal Love?
A coming-of-age episode?
What's your answer?
I thought it was a very youthful episode of Equal Love.
An episode of youth in Equal Love.
What? The funny kind?
The funny kind.
Not live performances?
No, not really. Really. But I'll say it. I'm on the move.
Okay, okay. Okay, okay. Okay, okay.
What the hell? On the bus?
Something like that.
On the bus?
Where is it? Where are you on the move?
Which part of the trip are you on?
I don't know!
The fast one. The fast one.
The fast one? The fast one.
Is that a bus? Shinkansen?
I don't know.
Correct. I don't know!
I'm right too.
It's right there.
But I'm sure it's etched in Yoli's memory.
I'm sure it's etched in her memory.
Yes!
What do you think?
Here we go!
Ready!
I think this is the seat,
Ugh.
Where is it?
I don't know.
Youth boy.
For sure.
I do it a lot, so I said it's etched in my mind.
I used to send photos from my "Cheer Up" folder to everyone on the bullet train.
There it was, there it was.
We all sent each other the very first time it started.
Oh, that was here.
Shinkansen.
I feel different and I'm not sure anymore.
I'm not sure either.
Both are good. Youthful.
What's your answer?
I don't know.
We were all on the bullet train on the move,
Someone posted a really funny picture to our funny folder,
And we all giggled and laughed the whole train ride,
It was fun, like the night of a school trip.
It was indeed.
Correct.
That's great. You've pinpointed it right.
It's here now, BiFB.
And I sent it yesterday.
I did send it.
I sent you my picture.
That day was fun.
It was fun.
Everyone try not to say anything.
They were giggling the whole time.
It was so funny.
It was fun.
Points.
1.5.
I crossed the Shinkansen.
0.2.
Gentle. Gentle.
Kind.
Thank you.
Current points?
1.5.
1.2.
0.3.
So I guess we have two more questions.
Let's go to the second question.
The second question from the bottom of the last.
The second question from the bottom.
If you had to say, what would you like to see fixed more than Noguchi?
Do you say that a lot?
Everyone does.
Emotionally, how do you feel?
Like, "Oh, no!"?Like, "What a pain in the ass!"?
Like it's a little bothersome?
Here we go again.
I can think of too many reasons.
Is this it?
Seino.
Second question.
We are all alike, aren't we?
That's what I'm talking about.
That's what I'm saying.
It's equal here, right?
Third question.
Go ahead.
The part where she keeps saying she's cute but she's not.
Ah.
That's close. 0.4.
No, it's high. It's high. It is.
Popular. 1.9.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
But you don't like Ioshan? He says that a lot.
0.2.
Oh, 1.4. That was close.
That was close. I got a score.
Now it's 1.9, 1.4.
Last problem. Let's go for it.
Let's go for it. Good luck.
Well, let's see if we win. Go ahead.
This is my third favorite thing about Ojita.
Why third? Third?
I don't know what third is. I don't know.
It's hard to say.
There was an episode, but I didn't talk about the episode,
If you hit the episode.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
It's so hard.
Yesterday.
Yesterday. There was one yesterday.
I can express it with my hands or something.
I don't know. I don't know.
It can be expressed with a hand, one hand.
I don't know.
I'm writing a lot.
Okay? Thank you.
Okay.
Bright.
Simple.
Bright. Simple.
When MCing or speaking, move back and forth,
I'm going to do it like this.
I'm going to do it.
He said he could express himself with one hand,
You're really good at this. I'm going to do it.
This is it.
That's the egghead.
It's embarrassing to be told.
I do it so much.
I can't listen to it. I can't hear it either.
It's over.
Last question.
Answer, please.
Third favorite part?
Well, you always do a good job.
You did it. You did it.
What do you think?
You've seen Kana do a good job, right?
Have I?
You said, "I want to do this at the concert.
During the show, I said, "I want to do this, so I'm going to do this," and she said, "Try it,
And that went well during the show.
And after that, during the live performance,
What a great episode.
Yes, he did it during the show,
I like the fact that you always give me confidence like that.
This is totally different.
It was a good episode.
I got all the questions!
So fast!
Hana-chan got 1.9!
I got 1.4!
So, Hana-chan wins!
Thank you!
That's great! That's great!
That's great!
It's only 1.9, though.
That's great.
I didn't know scores could be that chopped up.
Indeed.
Please keep an eye on this 00 King!
So, that was King Otani!
Bye bye!
andere